bsmart.in 2010-05-09

# Privacy Policy

Home Privacy Policy

Smart Wireless Pvt. Limited is an Essel group of company.

This Privacy Statement sets out the Company's policy relating to the collection and use of your personal information on www.bsmart.in. This statement applies in addition to the Site's Terms of Use.

The Site may contain links to other websites. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of those other websites.

The Company believes that the responsible use of personal information collected on the Site is an important element of its business operations and critical to its reputation. As part of the Company’s commitment to your privacy and respect of your rights, the Company adheres to this Privacy Statement in the operation and management of the Site.

By submitting identifying data, a visitor to the Site is agreeing to the Company's use of such data as described in this statement. Should you have questions or concerns about this statement or should you have any queries regarding any personal information relating to you which may be in the Company’s possession, please feel free to direct your enquiry **_to_**

The extent and type of information the Company receives from you depends on what you do when visiting the Site.

If you visit the Site to read or download information, such as news items, case studies, or capability statements, much of the information the Company collects - such as the domain from which you access the Internet, the date and time you access the Site, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to the Site - is statistical only and not personally identifiable. The Company uses information about the number of visitors and their use of the Site in aggregate form to make the Site more useful and attractive to you.

Generally, the Company only collects identifiable information that is specifically and voluntarily provided by a visitor to the Site. Typically, the Company obtains limited identifiable information from visitors, such as name, title, address, email address, and telephone and fax numbers. For example, if you send the Company an email message requesting information about the Company, your email address and other information you supply to facilitate a response to your request will be used by the Company for that purpose.

Demographic information, including gender and occupation, is not actively sought, but may be submitted when a visitor responds to an online job application. If you send the Company a resume or CV to apply online for a position with the Company or any of its subsidiaries, the information provided will be used to match you with available opportunities. It is not the Company’s intention to seek any sensitive information through the Site unless legally required for recruiting purposes. It is suggested that you do not provide sensitive information, but should you wish to do so for any reason, the Company accepts your explicit consent to use that information in the ways described in this privacy statement. CVs are retained in soft copy in a secure location, completely discrete from the Site, until such time as the Company’s recruitment staff decide the CV’s are obsolete at which time the CV’s are removed from the Company's internal file system. At all times CVs and other personal data submitted as an online job application are treated in strict confidence and accorded appropriate security.

When a visitor provides personal information to the Company, it is used solely for the purposes for which it was provided. Personal data collected may be transferred to other companies or offices within the SMS Management & Technology Limited Group of Companies, where appropriate, to meet the purpose for which you have submitted the information. The Company’s policy is not to share personal information with third parties, unless required by law nor to sell personal information to others. Your personal information will be retained only for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes for which the information was collected or as required by law.

In some areas of the Site, the Company employs ‘cookies’ (small data files that are sent to your computer) to improve your experience of the Site however, these are not used to track individuals or record information about you. The use of ‘cookies’ is now fairly standard operating procedure for most websites, but most browsers permit you to reject or disable the cookies if you wish.

The Company recognises that your information is valuable and it takes all reasonable measures to protect your information while it is in the Company’s care. Details on How to Access Personal Information and How to Make a Complaint are included in our Privacy Policy.
